"use strict"

export const quizData = [
    {
        question: `Correct syntax to output "Hello World":`,
        a: "System.out.println()",
        b: "print()",
        c: "Hello World",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Create a variable with the numeric value 5:",
        a: "integer num = 5",
        b: "num = 5",
        c: "int num = 5",
        d: "num = int 5",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Method to find the length of a string:",
        a: "strlength()",
        b: "length()",
        c: "str.length()",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Operator used to add together two values:",
        a: "+",
        b: "-",
        c: "*",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Operator used to compare two values:",
        a: "<",
        b: "<",
        c: "=",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "COMMENTS in code:",
        a: "//",
        b: "**",
        c: "isComment()",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Array, variable type with:",
        a: "[]",
        b: "{}",
        c: "()",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Create a method:",
        a: "method() {}",
        b: "method()",
        c: "create method",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Keyword used to create a class:",
        a: "Class",
        b: "new Class",
        c: "class",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Operator used to multiply numbers?",
        a: "+",
        b: "*",
        c: "/",
        correct: "b",
    },
]
